FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
UNREQUITED LOVE
Huh?
What?! Seriously?! That's
like really messed up, isn't it?
Yeah! Right? And she totally knows
that Misato likes Koichi on top of it.
What's so great about her anyway?
- I wonder if Misato thinks she's cute too.
- She clearly does.
Kurumi.
- Let's be on the same team!
- It'll be great!
No way! You seriously
don't have a crush on anyone?
But you're so cute! What a waste!
- I'm so glad we became such good friends!
- Same here!
Right?
Being in the same circle is the best.
No way! Miyagawa said
that he liked Kurumi?
Seriously! What the hell? Miki's liked
Miyagawa for as long as I can remember.
Well, she has been... lending
Miyagawa her notebook and stuff like that.
She probably doesn't like it when any
of the guys like a girl who isn't her.
- She's just pretending to be interested!
- That's awful! Plus, she called
herself "Kurumi" when her names "Ume."
I only let her into our group because I
thought she'd make it easier for us to
- talk to the boys.
- Hey, guys! If she ever has a real
- crush, we should ruin it for her!
- She went out of her way to
- mess with us, so why not?
- Right?
Oh, hey... You haven't gone home yet...
- Something wrong?
- It's nothing.
You sure?
Yeah. You have practice, Kazehaya?
Mhm! I'm just grabbing
something real quick.
Oh I see.
I knew I left it here.
Good luck!
Thanks.
Seriously, you sure you're okay?
Whoa, what is it?!
He's so different.
He's popular and always surrounded by the
other boys... and yet he always sees me for
- who I am.
- Same class again?
I never told anyone about my
feelings... about what I felt for Kazehaya.
I put a lot of effort into him, didn't I?
More than I ever put into studying.
The whole reason I went to
Kitahoro High was to be with him.
Kazehaya!
We were placed in
different classes though.
What's up?
It's the committee's handout. I
was asked to deliver it to you. Here.
Oh, thanks!
Yeah. Those two are
perfect for each other.
There is something I want
to borrow from you, Kazehaya.
I'd always find an excuse to see him.
Oh yeah that's right, the CD!
Man, I totally forgot, my bad.
In hopes... He might start to look my way.
Practice for field day, huh?
I don't really wanna, but at least
having Kazehaya around will make it more
interesting.
Speaking of Kazehaya... The poor guy
was volunteered instantly, wasn't he?
Yup!
Hmm.
Oh that reminds me, Kazehaya's on the
Field Day Committee. He's representing
- Class D.
- Wow, is he really? Maybe you should
become a member of the committee also.
What? You think I should?
There's really no reason not to, so why
not try it out? This could end up being
how you and Kazehaya get together.
I don't think so. How many times do I
have to tell you that's not gonna happen?
Though I wouldn't actually mind
becoming a committee member. -See? So try!
I can't volunteer myself for the
position... It's too embarrassing.
Oh hey! I didn't know you
were on the Field Day Committee.
You're here too, Kurumi? That's great.
Guess we both have awful
luck, huh? Sit. That seat's free.
Oh, thank you.
- And also, thanks for that CD you lent me.
- My pleasure. Would it be okay if I
borrow one of your CDs in return?
Yeah, sure, that should be fine.
I've been hearing a lot of rumors
involving Sadako everywhere lately.
I mean, she did make a
big scene the other day.
Wonder what kind of girl she
really is. I don't know much about her.
Oh yeah, didn't we see her
hanging out with Kazehaya before?
Oh yeah, I remember that. And we were
both saying stuff like "Oh my gosh, are
- the two of them dating now?"
- There's no way that would ever happen!
You think so?
If Kazehaya did actually like
her, would it be that weird?
Of course, it would! She'd
never even stand a chance!
Kazehaya's a total good guy, so
naturally he's gonna be overly nice to
her!
- Huh?
- Besides, if he liked
anyone, it'd be you, Kurumi.
- No, that's impossible.
- What are you saying? You
- two are so close, aren't you?
- That's only 'cause we both
- went to the same middle school.
- Jeez, why don't you
two just go out already?
- Not happening.
- Even if you don't feel that way, maybe
Kazehaya will eventually fall for you.
You've given power to me too...
and I want you to know that.
The Kazehaya I had come
to know... was changing.
It's her fault!
Yeah! Sawako ruined things between us!
Kazehaya.
- Oh...
Oh, Sawako, you're sweating like crazy!
Huh?
Uh...
Thank you.
There, all good.
Oh that's right, was
there something you needed?
Not really, I just came
over to talk to Sawako.
Since the two of us have become
friends after all, right, Sawako?
I'm your fa...
Frie...?!
Yeah, we're friends... I
mean, obviously, right?
What?!
- Eat and then nap probably.
- I can't just let her have him.
- Really? Lunch already?
- And then a little siesta, huh?
Trash?
I'll do whatever it takes.
SAWAKO KURONUMA
You see? I told you. Well,
let's give them all our support.
Ka... ze... haya?!
W... Why?
Why?
Why?!
It didn't work out as planned in the end.
Why couldn't it have been me?
I've always... always watched over him.
Longer than Sawako. Way longer.
Kazehaya...
I wonder... What would have happened if I
had asked him out before he ever met
Sawako?
I'm such an idiot.
It's impossible. No matter how hard
I try... It's his decision to make.
So then, does that mean you can't
see me being a good match for Kazehaya?
Huh? No, that's not what
I'm trying to tell you at--
Okay, then I... I really want
you to support me, Sawako.
You're the only one I've ever opened up to
about my feelings like this. Do you think
there's another person who would be
a better match for him or something?
- It's not that. You'd be a great match.
- Thanks, Sawako. Then you...
But... Oh.
It's just, I... I can't support
you from the bottom of my heart.
So, that's why I can't help you.
If I'm honest with myself... Well,
I also think of him as special.
So, I can't do
anything for you. I'm sorry.
Even if I can't help you directly, I
understand. And I know exactly what you're
feeling.
That's why, at the very
least, you can still talk to--
Shut up.
Why don't you let it go?
This is the part where you realize the
difference between us and you back off.
I'm hearing a strange voice coming from
her direction. I- Is someone hiding behind
her or something?
Sawako's such an odd person...
Honestly, she's straight up weird.
Kurumi!
Don't call me that
anymore. No more "Kurumi".
- Oh, Ume it is.
- Urgh... Urgh...
You know what, Sawako? The other day I
made sure to write your name down in my
notebook. It's for, well, girls
like you. Girls who call me Ume.
Sawako Kuronuma... Sawako Kuronuma...
Sawako Kuronuma... Sawako Kuronuma... Sawako
Kuronuma... Sawako Kuronuma...
Sawako
- Kuronuma... Sawako Kuronuma...
- What?!
I- Is that okay? I mean you...
Huh? You're gonna ask that now?
Really? Whatever, I'm done talking to you.
Ume, hold on a second!
- Stop calling me that name!
- Oh, then, what do I call you?
It's an insecurity... my only one
"Ume" is... kind of my Achilles' Heel
Don't treat my feelings
the same way as yours.
Are you saying that you
actually know things about him then?
I've always watched Kazehaya. It's
something I've done ever since we were in
middle school together. So then, whenever
I would see him talking to other girls,
I'd intervene and try to
prevent him from dating any of them.
You...
You've worked so hard.
Oh, well yeah, of course I have!
But anyway, the point is, I can
confidently say I know Kazehaya quite
well. And it's not as if this is
anything new either. Like I was saying,
I've watched over him forever.
With Sawako... It doesn't matter the person
or the circumstance. She faces everything
head on. Whether it's
with Kazehaya... or even me.
I told you you're in my way!
I said that I hate you for being around
Kazehaya when you never even worked for
it! I had assumed with you,
I'd have no trouble winning.
Because nothing you do could ever
compare, since I... I've always... always
liked Kazehaya.
And I'm sure of that.
Kurumi, I hope that this doesn't sound
weird or anything but compared to when I
first met you, I truly think
you're much cuter now than you were.
I know I'm cute, that's not the point!
But... but what good is being cute?
If Kazehaya doesn't like
me back, it doesn't matter!
It just hurts...
Because I know he doesn't feel the
same way about me as I do about him.
Since I've... always been watching over him,
I could tell. Why did you come back here
anyway?
I can't believe I'm crying... with you
standing right in front of me like this.
I'm here because you know
Kazehaya's good sides. You said it
yourself.
So I thought, that you and I could
talk about them since we both like him.
I hate you...
Sawako's... so dense.
W- wait a minute, are you telling me
there's a chance that Kazehaya might like
me back?
Until a little while ago, I was a total
loner who didn't even have even a single
- person to talk to.
- It doesn't matter... Kazehaya
wouldn't judge someone for that.
He's kind and he looks after people.
- And he sees you for who you really are.
- Yeah and when he smiles, no matter
what, you can't help but smile with him.
Exactly! But also, if you mess up
with something important, he'll hold you
accountable. He's surprisingly
short-tempered, and he just hates when
people do the wrong thing.
Regardless of gender
everyone looks up to him!
He's honest...
And cheerful...
Cute... Why the heck am I
sharing all this with you?!
I love this.
I've never talked like
this... with anyone before.
Why'd this happen? It
should have been perfect timing.
We started high school and I even got
everyone to support the idea of us being
together. Now was the time to make
him fall for me... the perfect time.
But, in the end, it was all for nothing.
Earlier I... accidentally made Kazehaya
think that I like Pin Arai!
And no matter what I say now, he'll
probably assume I'm just denying it out of
embarrassment!
I was just going to completely give
up at that point. But then Sawako said...
Yes, it does.
I mean, I didn't want him to think
I liked Sanada. It felt awful being
misunderstood. I understand. So, I'm
sure he will too if you just talk to him.
You think that he'll understand
everything as long as I just "talk to
him"?
Are you stupid?
See ya.
Kaze--
Oh, uh.
Cheer up, okay?
I don't want him to misunderstand.
No... Wait...
Kazehaya, wait!
You're wrong! Pin isn't the person I like.
The one I really like is... you, Kazehaya.
It was always you. Only you.
Oh Kazehaya
Please stop thinking I like someone
else. I just can't... I can't take it!
I'm so sorry about that, really!
I'm an idiot... I'm sorry...
There's already someone I like.
It's impossible... for me to
see anyone else but her.
So, I'm sorry.
I know. It's so obvious.
Kazehaya, does me telling you that I
like you make you feel happy at all?
Yeah. Thank you.
Just this once... Call me by
my name, okay? My first name.
Ume.
Well, I suppose this granny name
isn't as bad as I thought then!
Man, saying all this stuff wasn't my
intention. I really miscalculated.
Miscalculated?
Kazehaya... You have no eye for girls!
See ya!
I said it.
It was so unlike me to
do something like that.
But ever since then, I haven't used my
"People who called me 'Ume'" notebook a
single time.
Will he accept this?
If I had to bet...
Sawako's will be homemade.
TO TOMO, TO AYANE,
TO CHIZU, SANADA, EKKO
Neither Ayane nor Chizu... come off
as the types to make any themselves.
This'll be my first and last
time giving him chocolates.
All right! I'll use my most
expensive face mask tonight!
Even though I want to give them...
My heart hesitates.
Next time: "Valentine"